[Home](https://www.webhostingsecretrevealed.net/) / Privacy & Cookie Policy

Privacy & Cookie Policy
=======================

Privacy Policy
--------------

You may provide certain personal information, such as your first and last name and email address, when you subscribe to our newsletter or download our free resources.

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell or otherwise provide personal information to other companies for the marketing of their own products or services. We will retain your personal information for as long as your subscription is active or as needed to provide You services or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law (e.g., to comply with a subpoena, warrant, or court order) and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, avoid litigation, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, and/or respond to a government request. We may also disclose information about You if we determine that such disclosure should be made for reasons of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance.

Third Party Services & Ad Networks
----------------------------------

We work with third-party vendors and ad networks to serve ads on WebHostingSecretRevealed.net.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your visits to our site and other sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Google Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated) or [AboutAds.info](https://optout.aboutads.info/).

Website Cookie Policy
---------------------

WebHostingSecretRevealed.net ([WHSR](https://www.webhostingsecretrevealed.net/)) uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience.

#### **What are Cookies?**

Cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts and affiliate link clicks, and provide tracking data to third party applications like [Google Analytics](https://www.webhostingsecretrevealed.net/blog/web-tools/what-does-google-analytics-do-and-how-do-i-get-started/).

As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better.

#### **Disabling Cookies**

However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser.

You can change your browser settings by clicking the appropriate link as follows: [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer), [Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en), and [Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/278835/how-to-delete-cookie-files-in-internet-explorer).

We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at [the About Cookies website](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which offers guidance for all modern browsers.

Relevant pages: [Terms of Service](https://www.webhostingsecretrevealed.net/tos/) . [Earning Disclosure](https://www.webhostingsecretrevealed.net/disclaimer/)
